Pete Welding collection, 1958-1995
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 9: Photographic materials
  - Subseries 2: Black-and-white negatives
    - Miscellaneous photographs, 1958-December 23, 1968, 149 photographs: black-and-white film negatives; 120 mm (roll format); 2 photographs: black-and-white film copy negatives; 4 in. x 5 in. or smaller (Box 28)
      See box-folder 24/7 for black-and-white prints.
  - Subseries 3: Color slides and negatives
    - Son House, Jimmy Brewer, Thomas Swain, undated, 8 photographs: color transparencies; 120 mm (slide format) (Box 29)
      See box-folder 21/27 for black-and-white prints.
    - Fred McDowell, March 1968, 12 photographs: color transparencies; 120 mm (slide format) (Box 29)
      See box-folder 22/4 for the black-and-white prints, and Box 28 for the black-and-white negatives.
    - Quicksilver Messenger Service, April 3, 1968, 15 photographs: color transparencies; 120 mm (slide format) (Box 29)
    - Johnny Shines, 1960s, 19 photographs: color transparencies; 120 mm (slide format) (Box 29)
    - Maxwell Street, undated, 57 photographs: color transparencies; 120 mm (slide format); 6 photographs (2 strips): color film negative; 35 mm (roll format) (Box 29)
      See box-folder 24/2 and 24/3 for black-and-white prints.
    - Miscellaneous records, undated, 2 photographs: color transparencies; 120 mm (slide format, unmounted); 2 photographs: color transparencies; 35 mm (slide format) (Box 29)
- Series 10: Sketches
  - Big Joe Turner, undated, 1 sketch: probably pencil on paper; 7 3/4 in. x 9 in. or smaller (Box-folder 25/7, Subfolder A)
    Drawing by Pete Welding; originally housed in box-folder 25/3. Probably pencil on paper.
  - "Practising [sic] the Piano," undated, 1 sketch: probably pencil on paper; 7 3/4 in. x 11 in. (Box-folder 25/7, Subfolder B)
  - "Elmer Snowden on the Frank Ford Show," July 20, 1960, 1 sketch: probably pencil on paper; 7 1/2 in. x 5 1/2 in. or smaller (Box-folder 25/7, Subfolder C)
    Drawing by Hank Newmark; originally housed in box-folder 24/8. Probably pencil on paper.